Welcome to the Baxter building.
We make a point to do family dinner
every week.
Sunday at 7:00 on the dot no matter
what, we're all here.
Herbie, how's that sauce coming?
Yeah, I'll be the judge of that.
Okay.
Okay,
is this guy good or what?
I want to add a couple cloves of garlic.
Not because it's not delicious, I just
want to add a little bit of zip, okay?
T minus five.
Before we went up the first time,
you couldn't turn invisible.
Ben wasn't a rock.
The best pilot in the world right here.
Yeah.
Best looking he means.
And Johnny never caught fire.
Ben has always been a rock.
Johnny is Johnny.
Hi.
And I'm right here.
Whatever life throws at us,
we'll face it together.
As a family.
Fantastic four.